<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SLAG</string>
    <string name="OurMissionIntro">The amount of e-waste generated in Singapore is growing very fast as technological advancement leads to faster product replacement. In Singapore, more than 4 million people own more than one electronic device, and with the growing industry of technology, more and more electronic devices are made and consumed every year. The technological advancement leads to faster product replacement.   It is estimated that 60,000 tonnes (60 million kg) of e-waste was generated in the year 2017. With such a huge amount of e-waste being thrown away, it has a huge impact on the environment as most electronic devices contains small amounts of hazardous materials, which requires proper disposal. Improper disposal of electronic devices can not only cause major environmental pollution, but could also harm humans and our planet.</string>
    <string name="OurMissionOurTask">To create a simple system to build public awareness of e-waste to the neighbourhood around Woodlands, using our E-Waste bins, and the providance of information on how to properly dispose E-Waste.</string>
    <string name="ContactUsPlace">9 Woodlands Ave 9</string>
    <string name="ContactUsPlaceMore">Republic Polytechnic S.L.A.G Building, Singapore 738964</string>
    <string name="importance">The recycling of electronic waste protects the health of people and the environment. Incorrect disposal of electronic waste causes environmental pollution, which can be harmful to human health. Keep e-waste out of landfills. Computers, mobile devices, televisions, sound systems, chargers and even household appliances are all recyclable, yet they can also be the most dangerous materials dumped inside a landfill, according to the Environmental Protection Agency. When improperly disposed of, the heavy metals, plastics and glass in e-waste can pollute the air or seep into waterways. Recycling e-waste can significantly decrease the demand for mining heavy metals and reduce the greenhouse gas emissions from manufacturing virgin materials.</string>
    <string name="importance2">The recycling of electronic waste also helps to preserve our sustainable natural resources. The recycled material is used to produce new products. This reduces the need to produce mineral raw materials from land with limited supply. Reducing mining needs also reduces pollution as the mining process affects our environment.</string>
    <string name="howto">You can properly dispose E-Waste starting with using our E-Waste bins around the neighbourhood. Dispose your E-Waste in our bins, where we will send our collectors to collect the E-Waste and send them off to recycling companies. We can also reduce the amount of E-consumption by limiting the number of devices we replace every once in awhile.</string>
</resources>
